Yeah, but I just I just wanted I just wanted to start a new stream
Nothing really happened, but it's already a fresh stream
Hello chibi-chibi
Yeah, well, yeah
Hi guys
Hey, Jamie's Cowboys is not number one place now see number two. I think it doesn't I guess it goes by the
It goes by when the chat starts who starts who's commenting and stuff
No, it says nine watching bisquick right and bisquick number three. Oh, basically number three in my chat
Congratulations, bisquick. You're number three
chibi chibi
Oh, you got the elders back
She's mad she's so mad
Because she don't you know she can't fucking finish the live and she's not gonna pay for your membership
Oh, no, she's not gonna pay for it
God damn that was that was beautiful
Beautifully done, baby
Well, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I don't, I
From behind
Yeah, guys, but pretty cool. I didn't notice that they were doing the the rankings now
I guess it guys is the first time you saw that in my chat or like the last episode the first time you saw that
That just seems like I just started
Like you know, sometimes you just institute it right in the middle of the stream
If I was on waiting list or something that
It's asshole. Hey guys, you know, we can always you know, we've had a really good membership drive earlier tonight
I don't need a couple of memberships, you know, we had a
Smelly and you know, Jamie donated for a couple of memberships
We're we're appreciating the the family I'd love to see you all get a membership and like
I will see your name easier.
Plus, I'll give you more cards in the readings.
I hope the last reading, like they're upstair,
if I ended in the middle of it,
but I think that was the message
that person was supposed to hear.
You're bound to be out of the top three, yeah.
Yeah, so I'm getting a teriyaki burger tonight.
I'm getting a coffee milkshake.
You know, it's a little bit pricey.
A teriyaki milkshake.
No, no, no a teriyaki burger and then uh, and then a
No thing we only guys only live once you know and so and also live in the moment enjoy
You know enjoy enjoy life while we can right your number three second loser
Yeah, now see everyone's fighting 19 people already in chat for three minutes. This is how it should be guys today
It was like a lot of the chat man. Shout out to the chat
Yeah, how are you doing? How's this house things going?
Jamie's Cowboys. Thank you. You know, Jamie's Cowboys. Ldo is a mod. Jamie's Cowboys
DJ lecture is a mod
He-man is a mod and
Rado is a mod and so so how many you got five now? Are you
I want to keep it. I want to keep it at five. I want to keep it at five
You know, so do you know he man? Who is he man because he man is always in Kate's chat
We have
I know he has actually a woman he managed it's a very masculine name for actually a woman
Oh, so you do know her so you know her? Yeah? Yeah, I know he man and she's gonna hear all this at the beginning
She's a good great mod to get supporter. I don't think anybody I don't think any of the mods
Anybody's gonna have anything they're very fair. I don't usually do anything in the chat
I've done shit in it like a long minute ago, but I don't I don't
Yeah, unless you say something, I won't be doing something unless it needs to be done. You know, I'm saying he's a town
It's gonna list it. Oh
I didn't know that though. Oh
Yeah, and then be the dick called a police on Kate that is confirmed. So I guess since people know yet
That's what she was showing me
It's summer summer's number six summer like yeah, it's like guys. This is fun
Yeah, also, I'm sorry, Christine at Chris Christine and Schmelly. Um, they did
That's gonna work though, but
We're gonna have a breath. We're having fun tonight guys, but I'm getting a burger delivered
Maybe I'll go over someone else's chat and stuff or we can have fun like we used to and we used to have like all this fun
It's like going to other people's chest
They're people to try to ruin it
But now I think the people like that we're trying to ruin it
I think they just got bored with my show or something that like so many people disappear
But it was like most of the people that were just talking shit. So it's like kind of good, right?
And I think it's also guys. I think it's cuz I've been doing Psalms. I've been doing sage. I've been doing
You know prayers. I've been doing
Positive thinking hey the Salinas a lot of people will stop fucking with you when you take the wrenches, too
So that plays a role. Yeah. Yeah, and I took the wrenches, but you know what?
Vita called the cops and someone I'm not sure I said this story I heard you know what the wrench is like
You know, there's people that are really great
People like I might refrain only say hey
I like I want this person to be a mod because I trust them and they've always been kind to me and
I just want to show my appreciation
And maybe I'll do something like I just did but otherwise I'm not gonna make any video mod
I don't want you asking for a mod. I just want you know people to enjoy the show while they're here
because if you're a mod you're just kind of proven that you're a supporter of the show and
And they
There's sassy scarlet goes right
That's a scarlet anyway, but you legit had the case of she got the screenshot from Cade live
Yeah, well, I know that they're not supposed to put stuff. I mean, but that's why people can put like
Things in the chat. They can put information. You can take a screenshot of the chat and there was like, oh, yeah
There's proof that they're putting it. I mean, it's like, you know
Right. Yeah, sassy, you know, I see I see you. I see you supporting me
You know, and you're my books here. Yeah, so, you know
I think I just have good people watching out for me and everyone was good watching out for me
but I had way too many mods and
Drama over the mods and stuff like that. They're cracking down on dogs
I know they're cracking down on dogs thing after that the whole the whole thing with the other case and stuff like that, so
Yeah, see like it's in Jamie. Jamie's glad you ever run because hey country girl
Guys, we don't know where this world is going. We don't know where the world's gonna go
What's gonna happen? You know that the world can change in half a second
and everything goes topsy-turvy and
We're crazy rulers can come into power
The whole whole world can change overnight
We just gotta you know work this is like our time
If fucking Kate get arrested I'm gonna lie for what she's doing like I'm gonna go live
I'm going to get that body cam.
I don't care how much it costs.
I just want to have to say that, you know,
because I heard Bita, you know, Bita went through it today.
And, you know, she got it reported.
You know, Kate's name, full name, Adri, all that.
Hey, Paige, going to come up and say that at Elzo.
You know, I don't know why I ask Kate numbers, so she's probably
going to call her ass.
Elzo, have you ever been paged at Elzo?
Okay, you have
Yeah
Where is tent dog today? I don't know
Hey, you can't come up. Okay, she can't come up JT. Can you come up a Nancy?
I would love Nancy come up someday. I know everyone can I'm getting teriyaki
Burr a few minutes guys and I only had one beer, but look how drunk I am
But yeah, I was locked outside by his wife and unfortunately passed away. Oh, no
Yep
So yeah, we're seeing a lot more blue and green in the chat if you have money you can
Persecute anyone else and you know, yeah, well, that's sad
Just on your break. You'll come up after work. Okay. Yep. I'll try to stay around
I'm gonna have the copy shake and the burger come so maybe I'll be awake for quite a while
I love you to page and pay to sweetheart
Page page is also modern chat, you know
Doug D. Kate won't be able to afford a lawyer. Oh, come on. You know, there's you know, there's people who do pro bono and there was also
there's also
People appointed by them a state, right? Definitely different. I'd be able to afford a lawyer
Well, that's not I don't know, you know, I'm really against I've nothing against me and I think it's okay
I don't know her story. I think she's a mom. That's I like respect mom's a lot
Vita might not be bluffing her
Okay, let's see. Oh, she might not be bluffing on the money. She might not be bluffing
Damn, bro. I might have to fucking
Join to find out what's going on, bro. Even though I don't really
But I need to know what's going on man. My freshly made order is on the way
Hi, JT, do you want to come up and say hi?
So you see anyone come get the picture picture drawn to and I drew L though
It was the kind of like not the hardest picture, but you know, it's kind of a simple
Simple look to him now. You're hungry. I know why am I so hungry? I had I was like I'll eat subway
I'll be good for the night. I'm still hungry
We're the crowd. Oh the crowd. Oh, yes. I think we're talking about the crown the crowns are for
The top chatters like if you they're like the top because people were talking with the crowns and I was like, what are you talking about?
I had no idea cuz I couldn't see it if you took top fans for example
Jamie's Cowboys big time and Renault Liz are the top three, but
Arbitrarily because they have like 75. Oh, here's JG. Do you know JC? I'm elder
The Wolfman
Like he what's going on man. Hi. How are you?
Me doing man. I haven't been here in a while. I really haven't been keeping up with shit, but
Hopefully things have calmed down a little bit. Oh
Yeah, it seems a lot better
That's good. Yeah, and we've had a really exciting time with a lot of donated memberships
Thank you guys so much for Christine smelly
You know and a lot of other people elder elder donated some members of Dougie D
Jenny Jen Jen
Everyone who donated memberships. I'm sorry if I'm forgetting anybody but thank you guys. Oh, Dougie Doug yet
Thank you guys so much for donating memberships like a big chat family growing
Yeah, so see how to elbow
Although sorry, can you unbend somebody for me on your band list and give them a second chance? Yeah, who's that?
Zen pause
I am banned already today. They're on band. This is me. It's a major nation
You sure he just text me don't try to type. Yeah, he tried to type
I just I just unbanned them fools. I don't know if you got rebound. I'll be right back
No, I don't think I actually met I don't think I met you although I mean, I think you know about me
But I don't think I've actually met you before
We definitely met
Well, oh shit, maybe it beat us. Maybe
Yeah, I am ban Zimples earlier today, so they just haven't tried typing the chat tonight, so I
Remember you'd be to get a report me. I don't know ban check. Oh, they see I told you Zimples is right there. See I told you
Yeah, simple simple sent me a cash-up donation
So if someone's band and it's like, you know, that'll get my attention if they send me a cash-up donation
If you got banned
Yeah, I told you I told you I banned you usually I'll just go right away and check and usually give them another chance
Because they're you're supporting my show and enjoy it
Yeah, but well the zimpful is where you're saying something rude about me or you made me you upset me in some way
So bug with me. Yeah, you know I
I'm
Are you doing you're still doing the readings right like the yeah, are you on reading tonight?
Yeah, what the heck why not? It's been a while. Okay?
JT wants to read. Let's get it to you
This one doesn't feel as active. It's a JT. Let me just chuckle a little bit. It's always better when you shuffle
You're a good shuffle
Sometimes cars pop out. They're called poppers
Sometimes cars just will feel right
Oh, okay, this one feels really right for you. Okay. Okay, okay
Seven of coins, okay, seven of coins
Seven is so seven is gonna be the chariot card and then the coins, you know, that's some material things
This is really going forward
There's some kind of material venture
and you know you have you know you have a lot of seeds planted they're growing a
lot you know you're doing pretty well it says seven of coins says you've had a
lot you've got a long path ahead of you are working hard
to set yourself for success.
Seven of Coins advises you to make decisions
with the long-term in mind.
Careful planning, now we'll leave to big rewards
in the future.
Okay, so there's been some plans in the works.
You've been planning something
and it looks like it's gonna go pretty well, okay?
Also, what do I have for you?
Okay, but there's been like some sadness.
Okay, there's been some sadness.
What's the saddest thing?
You've been sad about something
or you're sad about something maybe right now too.
regretting something some kind of regret it says the five cups because the cup
it's usually like the guy looking out kind of like crying over the water but
It doesn't have to be so bad.
It says, five of cups, it says,
Drat, your plans have been foiled.
Disappointments can be demoralizing
rather than ruminating on things that can't be changed.
Five of cups advise you to accept the circumstances
as they are and move on.
There are other opportunities waiting for you.
So maybe there was something that didn't work out.
It didn't have to be that serious.
It just has to be like, you know,
maybe some kind of disappointment with something, you know,
and we all have disappointments and...
We can all move on from them, right?
But yeah, I think that might be something
in the present energy.
And finally, oh, we have this night of cups.
I love this is you.
I don't know if you like reflecting.
Night of cups, it's a Gaston, right?
And night of cups, you know, he's one of the nicer nights,
you know, but he also tends to rush in
and rush out of places.
I don't know if this is you or someone you know
or some kind of energy around you.
but this Knight of Cubs says the Knight of Cubs represents someone who's
charming, handsome, and strong like Gaston Wright. The tarot card symbolizes the
ideal suitor ready to sweep you up your feet. Is it time to strike up a band and
celebrate or are you longing for something else? The tarot card advises you to
follow your heart. Okay so that could be you or
You know, I do I think you do have that energy that very step very strong handsome master than energy. That's very attractive, but I
See I can't say anything. What's your what's your sign by the way? Oh
Aries actually. Oh, so your fire sign. Okay. Well, yeah, you yeah, I got someone's air again
But you know the night of night of cubs usually is not
Not so bad, but nights, but there's still there's still out running around doing things instead of just being the king and like, you know
Ordering people around, you know, so you want to be able to get to that where you're seeing that we're giving the orders not
You know not following orders, right but uh
Cuz the night is always taking orders of the king the king is the point
I mean it's something that I've been working on is gonna gonna hat gonna happen right and then the cups are like something
Sadness and some kind of sadness. What is some emotion some emotion? Yeah, but I want to give you a I want to give you a
A card for advice. Okay, so here's the card for advice
Your card for your advice today is okay. It's a three of coins and three of coins is
Working with other people also
Other people might have been looking at you and saying wow
They've been like coming to you to see how you've improved in some way, and they're like wow you have improved
It's definitely some kind of part of collaboration. That's the word of advice. I would it would be like to
work with other people collaborate with other people even like people you consider
You know enemies or something like that. You can work with and you're you can you can
So it says just as scar has held from his hyena henchmen
The three of coins is a reminder that success often depends on your ability to collaborate and cooperate
Yeah, that's true
So that's you know, so don't you don't have to be a lone wolf about things
You know, you can collaborate cooperate and that will you know, hopefully
I think any sadness that might be present in the last reading will, will, uh, dissipate.
Let's see.
He was a prick.
Oh, Scar was a prick.
No.
I was just going to say Gaston was a prick.
Gaston.
Yeah, Gaston.
Scar was too, but yeah.
No, Gaston was a prick.
Yeah.
So how have you guys been? I have a burger coming. I've been in a coffee shake. Oh, what did you order? For where?
It's called the habit. It's called the habit. Oh, I do. I have tried them once. I like it. Yeah, they're good
Hey, beauty time or beauty is me. I'm sorry
Yeah, guys, I love having this an active chat and like I love I've been doing a lot more readings
There's been like just sick a lot
Still a lot a lot cooler. They'd lot less let's drama. Let's hate
But you know, even though it's not a dramatic earlier. I mean, I caught a little bit. I was
But yeah, they're over it. Yeah, they're over a hundred people in the chat earlier
Kind of it's not a kind of dramatic
It was getting it was being pretty dramatic as it was. Yeah
Can I read you? Yeah, and if you want like a you know, I'll put this banner if anyone wants like a you know
I'll do like a free reading for anybody
But if you want like a longer read tonight, you can get you a longer read
No, I just accept cash up. You know what's interested, but beauty is me, you know, I'll do a free reading for okay?
Beauty is me. Okay
Hold on
Okay, so five of wands. Okay, so this is like the poison apple. This is like there's been some kind of competition
You've been going through it could be a healthy competition. It could be a healthy competition, you know, but it's like, you know
If it's over some if it's over actual things
It can get I can get nasty if it's actually over
You know, you know just having fun something like that can be another thing
So I'm not sure you're compete you're competing with something. I don't know if you play sports or you're having problems with people
Okay, we got the sphere of cups. This is like
This is like this that third-party situation and it came in reverse
And so this is especially at maybe I would say some kind of negative third-party association
Somebody you've met through partying or something like that causing problems for you now
Somehow, you know, I'll tell you the three of cups reversed
It says
It says three of cups reversed shows you're feeling pressure to conform if there's disconnect between you and a group of people
We just the urge to change yourself to gain their approval
If it's not needed in any way stay true to yourself
Okay, I'll pull one more car for you. Okay. Hey, Jamie Rose come up on panel
Finally, oh, you got this moon card and this is a cool moon card you okay this moon card
You know moon is illusion a confusion
Fantasy things to be revealed secrets mysteries
We got this moon card 18 says
It says Emperor Kuwako is too self-absorbed to notice Yama's obvious attempts to steal his throne.
When the Moon Tarot card is drawn, it's a wake-up call, advising you to pay attention.
Don't take things at face value now.
Investigate contracts, deals, transactions, opportunities carefully.
Use your intuition if any hunches or gut feelings arise.
Trust them.
So there you go.
Hey, Jamie Rose, I think the link is pinned if you want to come up and say hi. It's a friendlier panel
It's not gonna be no one's in a harass you. I know it's like I've had some assholes up here before
harassing you
You know the other Jamie. Yeah
This is Lola. Yeah, Jamie. We're Jamie Rose. We have a genies cowboys
Hannah what's up Hannah?
Sassy
You go by birthday. Well, just so you can tell me your sign. I can tell you stuff about your sign
Yeah, I know some I know stuff about astrology, too
It's life long study though, you know, but yeah, thank you sassy. I love what you say that lover hate me
It's a leg for me, you know
Even cardio, okay, I want to be feel if you have some time tonight. I'm say hi
So you're Leo August or okay. Well, Leo's well, I can tell you I can I can do your birthday
Something called secret language of birthdays, but I'll tell you I can tell you some stuff beforehand. So Leo's
Always want to be the center of attention
always with the spotlight the sun they're represented by the rule by the Sun
They're sexy, but they're moody. They have tempers, right? Fire sign.
So your birthday is...
August 3rd.
Okay.
I'll see if this is the right link. Let me see.
Okay, so it says August 3rd. Is it August 3rd? Right? Am I right?
Hold on.
August 3rd. It says the day of the dangerous quest.
Those born on August 3rd are attracted to danger in one form or the other.
The quest usually involves placing themselves in harm's way or rescuing others from harm.
Their goal may be to reveal the truth as they see it, regardless of risk.
Too often it is the risk itself rather than the truth that is of most importance to them.
Those born in this day must be aware of endangering others through their activities.
Adverse to mundane experience, Augustan people often take excitement far from home.
Some indeed venture to the ends of the earth, while others summon the thrills of the imagination
from comfort of their easy-chair. Less highly evolved, Augustan people are simulated by the
excitement engendered by others and live victoriously.
Bicariously, most more highly evolved August 3rd people not only generate or experience
excitement firsthand, but also put it to work creatively or professionally.
August 3rd people may be at great risk of injuring themselves.
Usually no amount of persuasion from family or friends can deter them from their fascination
for conflict and risk.
Some look back on day-earing exploits as a test of the highest order in which failing
failing grades can't amount to destruction. Others are addicted to
instability and feed off peril as if it were food. Perhaps the most difficult to
dissuade are those fighting for a cause or defending an ideal. In this case, their
activity assumes a romantic or idealistic cast, although the nature of their
actions are more likely pragmatic or even cold-blooded if necessary.
For some born in this day, the notion of rescue also holds a central fascination, perhaps
manifested in their wish to physically rescue or protect someone, or bringing them psychologically
or spiritually to a safer, healthier place.
The rescue of Eurydice, Biorpheus, or the Israeli raid on Enneve in Uganda are the sorts
Perceiving themselves as heroes or heroines is important to them, whether it be the role
of adored parents, knight, and shining armor, or a Joan of Arc martyr.
August 3rd people must beware they're losing control over their egos.
In addition, they may mistakenly invest others with their own emotions or desires.
For instance, those that wish to save may in reality have a little interest in being saved by them.
A final danger is that the thrill of their adventures will wear off unless their stakes
are raised again and again like a drug high that can only be obtained by upping the dosage.
Thus, the addictive nature of their persistent search for excitement becomes, in many, but
not certainly in all cases, alarmingly clear.
Being able to harness such daring to productive ends will be a measure of their maturity and
Later, okay. Thank you
Hey, are you there? Oh?
There's a picture I
Drew that guys he loves it
You kind of does it kind of again? What is you saying? I
Love it. Are you there JT?
What sign are you you're born 823 82. It's your August 23rd. The
See where you go, let me see August
23rd sign
Your Virgo, yeah, your Virgo
We're gross your earth sign
I know there can be OCD. They can be variant cleaning, cleanliness. You're
planning along at work. Please make your acquaintance. Yes. Hi guys.
Oh, oh, you like your ear pain like that. Oh
Oh, oh, hey, Lola. Oh
Yeah, this is Lola
What was this? You're the sweetheart. I forgot to bring it up like this.
Isn't she cute? Yeah, cute.
She's a cute little kitty. It's Lola. Lola tricks his mom. A little nurse in here.
The nurse in here is looking at her. Look at Lola.
Lola is sitting over there looking at her kitty. Let's see where's my food.
Yeah, she just got the yellow green eyes.
We visited our pick-up counter, no.
That's my mistake.
Oh, no, no, no, no, he's on his way.
Phew, it said like, it said it.
But I ordered a teriyaki, charburger, and a coffee shake.
These won't stop away.
They already ate a Subway earlier,
but I'm just hungry tonight.
Oh yeah, so Jamie wants one?
Okay, Jamie got one.
Jamie, what have I got for you?
Jamie.
Ooh, Ace of Coins, some kind of new financial opportunity,
some kind of like, you know,
You know extra change you got, you know, you said there's something you got back something
Or some kind of like idea or seed or like something new with your business
some some kind of something new some kind of like
Kind of ace an ace and so it's something good. Oh and Jamie don't I keep getting this to get the hermit for you before
I think I get this hermit for you
You know hermit's just about spending time alone with drawing from the world
you know
Think I've got that for you a few times. Okay. Oh
And then magician. There's a magician. You get the magician. Okay, so Jamie
When you're after you spend this time alone, you're gonna be able to come out of it and like, you know, I think it's gonna help you
Master your powers or it's like control your powers or help you deal with your powers
You know, I know you've been having problems and like saying, oh, these are like curses and stuff like that. They're actually blessings
Yeah, this is a cool one
And there's a magician, he has the shadows behind him, right?
It might be for the collective, but I don't know if you get to have confidence in yourself
because I feel like some time withdrawn from everything will be like beneficial for you
because I know it can, and then you'll come out of it being able to manage things better.
Thank you, Jamie
Yeah, so you guys gonna have a mukbang. I guess I'll have a burger on my stream burgers
The coffee shake
Thank you, Jamie
Yep
Yeah, but I love you guys.
How are we doing guys in chat?
What's going on?
Is anything going on?
Should know about trade energy for energy?
Yeah, well, I think it's like, yeah,
it's an energy exchange.
I'm gonna see right now.
Yeah, I got some cigarettes.
I started smoking cigarettes now
because they stopped selling swishers here.
I would usually smoke in swishers,
but I was smoking these.
They don't have menthols anymore.
I just have these.
Cigarettes, I think are better for the camera. I think it's kind of look better
You listen to sad songs, Mousy
As soon as I do that
Sometimes I do that
So this is one step away
Within the next 15 minutes in the area. How are you guys doing?
Yeah, so I got I ordered like a really, uh, a really good nail pleating kit.
And thank you Zimpulse for the donation, by the way. Appreciate it.
If you become a member, I'll be even more sure not to let you
Be a member I'll give the members some leeway and being asshole, but you can behave yourself tonight
Where you from as opposed to you have blad the impaler are you into Elizabeth Bathridge?
I'm really into Elizabeth Bathridge more than blad the impaler. I mean with their clothes just brutal horrible horrible stories right?
Someday I'll tell you guys the stories of Elizabeth Bathory, who do terrible things.
Unspeakable things.
Oh, I hear cats kissing. Cats are kissing.
There's a every another page of the Illuminati trilogy like this book on or I just open to it says when Atlantis ruled the earth
The title appears in letters that look like blocks of stone tiled on top of one another to form a kind of
Step pyramid it's followed by shots of the earth as it looked 30,000 years ago during the great ice ages showing Willie
Mammoth saber-tooth tigers and chrome magnet hunters
while a narrator explains that at the same time the greatest civilization ever known
by man is flourishing on the continent of Atlantis.
The Atlanteans do not know anything about good or evil the narrator explains, however
they all live to be 500 years old and have no fear of death.
The bodies of all Atlanteans are covered with fur, as with apes.
After meeting various domestic scenes in Zyrkog, Gimeral, and Sergosa, the largest and most
central city on the continent, but not the capital because the Atlanteans do not have
a government.
We moved to the laboratory where the young, 100-years-old scientist, Grouad, is displaying
a biological experiment to an associate, Gao Tuong.
The experiment is a giant, water-dwelling serpent man.
He declares that he is bored, he wishes to change himself in some unexpected way.
Gouraud is already strange, unlike other Lancians he does not cover with fur, but only has short,
blonde hair on top of his head and a close crop beard.
In comparison to other Lancians he seems hazy naked.
He wears a high-colored pale green robe and gauntlets.
He tells Gao Tuan that he is tired of accumulating knowledge for the sake of knowledge.
It's just another guise for the pursuit of pleasure to which too many of our fellow Atlanteans
devote their lives. Of course, there's nothing wrong with pleasure, it moves the energies,
but I feel that there is something higher and more heroic. I have no name for it, but I know it exists.
Gauchuan is somewhat shocked. You, a scientist, can talk of knowing something exists when you have no evidence?
Gouad is dejected by this and admits my lens needs polishing, but after a moment he bounces back.
And yet, even though I have moments of doubt, I think my lens really is clear.
Of course, I must find the evidence, but even now, before I start, I feel that I know what I will find.
we could be greater and finer than we are. I look to what I am and sometimes I despise myself.
I'm just a clever animal, an ape, who is learned to play with tools. I want to be much more. I
say we can be what, illegal or even more, we can conquer time and seize eternity even as they have.
I mean to achieve this or destroy myself in the attempt.
You'll take one next Jamie's
Another card
We have a charburger you'll take one next
You get the wheel of fortune things are going in your in your favorite Jamie yet
We get the wheel of fortune again. Okay, you know what this means
Storytime and drawing time are fun. Yeah, that's the story time
There we go. We remember that spinning wheel in Cinderella. You know, she cricks her finger on it
But you know, it was stated that she was gonna do it like
And so since they knew we were gonna do it, it was supposed to be a horrible curse
She's a fairy godmother. She has some spiritual help or spirit guides. Maybe
They soften the curse and so they may instead of dying a fall asleep instead of this this will have it
And so it was it wasn't all bad
You know, and then she was able to overcome the curse eventually with the help of the fairy godmothers
Like the story time. Yeah, I got some great drawings of people. I'm gonna have a great whole book full of these great drawings
You like that one Jamie good
Yeah, I've drawn sassy scarlet John JT run left. Yeah, I have one left. I don't know. Oh, they say was leaving or he's leaving
Where does this appear?
You want two cars Jamie, so there's just you want two cars, okay, I'll get you two cars
Jamie Jamie Jamie. Oh the world cycle completed so you got this you know you got that
The other card you got the world, okay? I
Say Jimmy the end of it the end of a cycle completion you lead a cycle. We'll come in the next cycle. Oh my gosh
Hello, that's great. Yeah
You just burp you just burp all over
Where's that picture that is that picture of you?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, I spoke here
Mmm, I mean not really. I mean it's a really hard
Just a little bit. No, just that just that first. I was like, oh my gosh. Is it over melting?
That's good times. Oh, it's good times. What does he have on his face?
I think the megaphone went out
Oh, sorry. Okay, here we go. Are you gonna fail over?
Maybe maybe my bad
Oliver, are you mad at me? Are you mad at me all over?
Are you mad at me? Well, I've got like iPods, but they but they go in my ear
Are you mad at me? Are you mad at me?
Why why because like a lot of people like are talking shit about me and like you know, I wonder if you still like me anymore
No, whatever your shit with other people is y'all's business
Well, you don't care about
Bullshit, okay
You know comes they had a Oliver. Oh, well, you know all over some of the panel. Oliver's a good guy
Yeah, Jamie likes your cards. Yeah, you got two good cards
Yeah, oh, oh, it's arriving soon all over the point of my house
dropping my food right now the the door-dash people
fish tacos
No, it's a it's a teriyaki burger and
A coffee milkshake from the teriyaki burger is a teriyaki chicken
No, it's a teriyaki sauce on a hamburger
And it has like I think it has a has a pineapple in it, too
No, you can't do that
You can't do that to your body
That's pineapple a pineapple and teriyaki sauce on a burger
Yeah, it's liver. I'm gonna grab it right now. Move it back
You need ketchup
Any pickles? I'll check
And you need to see if that's all you need
You're not gonna be putting mayonnaise on your hamburger, that's wrong if you like
Burger King you're wrong and you need to figure stuff out in your life and why
you made bad decisions. You can put mayo on a chicken sandwich but you cannot
And you're not supposed to put mustard on your hamburger either, but you can do it or whatever.
It's not as bad. You can do it, but you're probably not going to go ahead and do it.
But that's your choice.
And if you put pineapple on your pizza, it's just...
It's just your choice. It's just your...
I
Will respect that much but no no mayonnaise on a
Ketchup pickle
Sometimes onions
It's like a good place with good onions and cheese and that's all you need
You don't need to put a Friday egg on top of your burger. That's stupid
You don't need this stuff. I went to one place and they stuffed the burgers with cheese and I was like
It's just there's no difference. It's just in the little stupid thing. Just put it on top. You dumb bitches
You don't need to put some spicy stuff on there. Good guy. You can put spicy stuff on your chicken if you really gotta
Do that, but I think people who like really spicy stuff are sick in the head
They're what do you call it?
Mast masochists. They're masochists
You probably like it when people kick them in the balls in the sexual life, but we won't go there
We're probably in the CBT if you know what that stands for
And if you don't know
Uh-huh, uh-huh
What is it fucking ball torture?
Here's that no I'm talking about these sickos out here
All the stuff that they're into that they shouldn't be
Good is good times in the clan
You know
Not that I'm aware of
He does have it. I think his interest says street might go back to Scotland. So he might be part of a clan
distantly
But I don't think he's part of the V clan
No, okay
And I don't think you would really join any club regardless of what he thinks
I don't think he would be he doesn't play well with others
It's so good coffee milkshake and he's he's
He's got a an injury a head injury that I think might be might affect him
No
Some there's some wounds that we can see with the ones we can't see especially in the brain
People have very damaged brains
Well, that's why I worry about scab me. I always tell him directly
You need to quit drinking but I knew somebody that had a really bad brain injury
And that's the first thing the doctors tell you you can't drink
Yeah, and it stopped your
brain from healing and he what do you what do you think about Bruce Willis is enough said
He's got dementia. You can't act anymore because you can't remember nothing
Hey, spunky, you know Oliver spunky comes out of all brown panel. Yeah. Hey Oliver
Look at all the look at all the green and blue in the chat. Are you jealous?
Yes
What I have to do is become a member or oh, I can renew my membership. I like to just again
No
Hello hi Oliver you there
Any Oliver's Oliver's muted out, but how are you?
Let's get him
Oliver you can't hear you come back up leave and come back up Oliver
Yeah
Yeah, but I was saying I was saying that it's that there is trauma and like sometimes people can look fine on the outside
But there's been there's trauma and so you don't know what's going on in the brain necessarily
There's a really good movie called the cell and Jennifer Lopez goes into this guy
He's a casserole killer and she can go into his dreams or his like you know in subconscious mind and you know and
She finds all kinds of
All kinds of traumatic things that happen to him in his past and
Maybe reasons why he was the way he was but
But it's just oh, so Oliver dropped off. But yeah, so how are you though?
I mean, I'm just getting a teriyaki burger having a coffee milkshake and
Yeah, I started smoking cigarettes again because they uh
They stopped selling a swisher sweets here anymore
Because they said it because it has the word sweet in it and so people think it's like they think it's like sweet for it
They get like a sweet thing or something and so
They take away switcher sweets black and miles like there's no cigar
There's all there is to get cigars and there's like the there's dins and there's chewing tobacco and stuff
You remember clothes when I was a kid I used to smoke clothes
Yeah, I would smoke those too. Yeah, they're a little bit intense. It's no great. Yeah
That's what got me started on cigarettes and then thankfully I don't smoke those anymore, but I
did pick up
looking vaping again
vaping yeah
Well, it probably is better. I think it probably is better for you. I don't think that you know, it does have this like a
What has a slide call or something this
Something that makes it
Smoke up when you when you exhale has some kind of chemical
Propylene glycol I think yeah, it's probably all bad. Yeah
Yeah, but I know I think a flirty diamond when it come up. Yeah, I can be your plug. You oh, yeah
So Florida I'm making it some flavored vapes and cigars. Yeah, I need some fruit
I want to get the menthol has been illegal in California for a few years now menthol is illegal
Cigarettes are like $10 a pack
There's no flavors. The only flavor you can have is like tobacco flavor. That's like doesn't the word
It's funny, I would only smoke menthols when I smoke cigarettes, but I only do the tobacco-flavored
razzes.
But they don't only taste like tobacco, it's kind of like a sweet, minty, I don't know,
I like it.
Yeah.
I like the camel crushes too, they had these camel crushes that were pretty good, you just
popped a little.
The ones that you, yeah, you popped a little thing, yeah.
Yeah, but now they're all illegal now they I mean they actually did have like another flavor like while the menthol was illegal
But now that even that flip that other flavor they had a like a
So they're kind of good flavor you can pop in there. So yeah, it's like it's uh
It's kind of slim pick it but maybe it's good that I smoke less smoking probably is bad for you
And I smoke enough weed and you know other stuff to like not
Everything yeah, everything good is bad, right?
Oh, we have flirty diamond on the panel. Hold on. Have you met flirty diamond? Hi flirty. I have not
Hey
Are you doing honey? I'm doing good. Yep. Good. The first time I ever went on this panel
My hair was down, but people were saying that I looked kind of like you
I mean
Lordy, can you came up for a second if you can?
Just show you the hey real quick
What are you doing, you know it was like I yeah my eyebrows aren't drawn in
Drawing your eyebrows in come on draw on your eyebrows real quick
Just for that what drawing your eyebrows real quick and come on camera. I'll take me like 20 minutes
Yeah, she took him off of the night. She's done. Yeah, my eyebrows
Put on put on dark glasses. I suffer from over teasing syndrome
You can't put on dark glasses put on dark glasses for a second
Hey, we're twins we're twins I mean shit
Well, you're both very pretty. Yeah, how's everybody doing? Yeah, so we had quite a day 30 diamonds
So are you an original demon? Are you okay? Have you talked since the show and yeah? Yeah? Yeah? Yeah?
We barely got off the phone
Yeah, but I never got the answer. So you're dating raging demon now. Are you e-dating I?
Don't I don't know you don't know
So okay, so we but he said he sent his dick pic. Is it that's the only picture he sends you or is he sent more pictures?
You know what I seen his toes before he said pictures of his toes
They're in an online situation ship
Okay situation. Okay, so and so you watched Titanic yesterday
We'd watch Titanic six six six
Oh, it's the horror version. Yeah, it's a horror version of it. It's on 2B actually. How was it?
Pretty much like the captain's
Granddaughter came came on the theme and like collected all the jewelry that was about to be sold
And then she like did some like seance and have all them like all the dead people like come back and haunt everybody and
Nobody survived actually so
It was kind of funny there was this influencer come this influencer couple on there
Unlike they
So like they kind of took some parts of the actual mechanic movie, but not fully
I'm flirty 30. Did you like they're like were you enraging demon like any naked on camera for each other during the movie?
Who has who hasn't seen me naked? I know but where you were you like?
You're doing other stuff during the movie like I mean like a little not I fucking I was screaming during the movie
I was I got scared. I was screaming
You have you had cyber sex with Virginia? Oh my god
Saki his dick is do you want do you want to see the pig that's been lurking around everywhere?
I well, I can't see his I can't see his dick on my shoulder. It's our
Okay, this D me on discord. Do you mean I want to I think he said it's okay. He said it's okay
I gotta ask region for that he barely forgave me for that one
Okay. Well, if anything, if it's okay, if it's okay, if he doesn't see you, if he doesn't see you, if he doesn't see you, well, I'm not going to share it. It's just for my eyes only. You can let him know. I'm very, very proud of it.
I mean, everyone on Discord has seen it. Kate, everyone on Kate's side have seen it already.
Have you been to Kate's tonight? I heard there was like drama going on with Kate.
Um, I was in her chat one time and I just said hi because we're...
She kicked me out of her Discord server.
She shared a video of me playing with myself two years ago, so I shared a video for slapping her ass, telling people to eat it.
And apparently, because she didn't do this publicly, I guess, I'm in the wrong.
Making myself, I mean...
A video of you slapping your ass versus quite literally playing yourself. It's quite sufficiently different, but you know
And then I was like, well, you're a whore and you post things on Twitter. I told her, okay, I'll make you a Twitter too
I'll promote you on Twitter. I mean fuck it
So yeah guys, I might make a cake the turtle Twitter account y'all y'all keep out keep the lookout for it
God he's a spunky blow me a kiss and lick your lips for me, please
Here one second. Well, yeah, okay, it's the best time people meet her ass though. She's
Why do you school, you know, it's cool because in a raging demon is like one of those I don't think he's a trans chaser
He's like open-minded where he's like
He doesn't he just doesn't care
No, what's that noise it was Kate telling people to eat her ass
Sorry, I'm a little messy
Regine is not a tranny chaser at any capacity
I might post Tranny Chaser content, but that don't mean people I talk to are actually a fucking Tranny Chaser.
Yeah, and that's a misconception people get, like the moment that someone talks to a trans person,
they're automatically labeled, and you know what? I'm mad because people stole my joke towards him
calling him a Tranny Chaser. I
You know, I used to joke around and call him one and now the joke another level
I would just call you a transistor. What was there a joke or?
Because I'm trans so that's why I would joke. I'm just I
Guess I'm mostly I guess I'm emotionally abusive or something
But I used to look around and call him a tranny chaser
But did he ever call you a predator or was that no no no no
No, that was like that was like somebody somebody made AI with you making him say that they put clips of his voice together
To make it sound like he called me one
So, you know, yes, I exposed his demon to everyone
But are you guys are cool now that you figured out? Yeah, we're cool now. I mean he understands that like I
Was in my
Editing now, right
You keep going back to that question, but are you are you aren't you you're like you're like talk on the phone for hours and you're like
You know, I will have region is about
Okay
He's like he's like, oh, what do you care?
Either way, it's like why do people care we're watching movies or like?
Sipping tea and smoking. Who cares? I just want to know what you're doing. I
Like that that's
We yeah, we just watch movies we smoke we talk about actual shit going on in our lives
That's all okay. Yeah, I've been you're having like in-depth emotions. That's good
It's not just like, oh, here's my titties.
And here's my, like, it's not just, like, you know,
it's not like that.
But is it happened, that happens too?
I should, Saki, I hear the photo of his dick.
Things happen, I guess, you could say.
But I shouldn't have done that.
I acknowledge that that's simply
something I shouldn't have done.
Was that a video?
Was that a video, or is that,
did he say a photo?
That's a photo.
That was a photo, okay.
No, I don't have a video. I don't have a video of Joker jacking off. Nobody else. Oh my gosh
It's when he paid me he said that to me
Hi
Hi good, how are you doing tonight? How are you?
Good, I'm fine
and
Bunky
The YouTube app so I can hear better good one second
My new friends guys
Now you're getting a bunch of new people up here
Very cool. Yes has been
a lot better lately.
I see my theory are mostly.
Gaudi, that was regarding Joker.
Joker has tricked on me
on a couple of times.
Everybody knows it.
Hi.
This is Brie.
Hi Brie.
Hi.
Good to see you Florida. I was saying don't give Dottie the tea. That's all he lives for. Oh, yeah
Dottie he he likes to sip hot boiling tea
You're not a porn bomber. Are you?
Bree
No, I'm not a porn bomber. I'm not a troll or anything like that. I'm just a body
I'm a porn bombers like you see my titties before
Yeah
It's I call them that the Hershey's kisses
Melted Hershey's kisses
Good, you know 30 and you got a slow roll porn bomber one day. I'm just gonna whip them out. I
Don't even know like when I did it. It's just people are calling my boobs implants. So I was kind of like
Hello, I said, it's okay if they are my door
No, I don't judge like I mean I considered getting implants before but like
Back in like the early 2000s or late 90s. If there was like some disease about the implants
I think it was because the leakage but the material just wasn't you know
Strong, I guess you could say I'm not a scientist or like surgeon or whatever. It's like
This is my logic behind it
Um, I thought about a fat transfer, but only 50% of the fat would survive
Yeah, that's the other thing as you go through all of that and then you only get like a little bit of a change
your body
I guess I could, you know, get some lipo with my stomach and transfer to my boobs, I guess.
But it's like, the lipo isn't even going to be like a lot of lipo-ing.
It's just kind of...
Just be careful if you do do something like that. Go to someone super reputable.
Yeah, because lipo is like a serious thing and like...
Yeah.
So, I mean, I thought about fat transfers, but I'm...
for me it's not what the recovery is. I'm going to do a boob job. I might as well do the real thing
at that point. You can always do, you know, the saline ones now. It's the silicone that they're
worried, you know, that causes that illness. What I have looked at though is the
The most naturalist, the most naturalist I've seen because I am there's guaranteed jiggle because of a fat transfer. Yeah. Well, I
I won't show my boobs, but if you go to a good surgeon, they can still save a lot of what
you have.
And if you go under the muscle, you'll still have good jiggle with the lift of fake boobs.
So it's pretty awesome.
Yeah, I've seen some girls, I mean, I've even seen trans women that have the jiggle after
the implants.
But it's like, I just, I don't want that bimbo look.
afraid of and like for me I still shake the like the very hard you know shit
like yeah I won't show my boobs but like you can tell they're definitely like
squishy oh yeah
So like you said, yeah, I don't want to hear about boo, but but yeah, like I can go without a bra
And that part is awesome. And but I still have like squishy boobs, which feel natural like
It's like a party trick for me to be like, hey, my boobs are fake, but feel them
So if you don't mind me asking flirty diamond, um, how old are you? You don't have to tell me it's just
Okay, cool. Well, I'm 30, and I had a best friend or whatever. She's she's not here anymore. She's now deceased or whatever.
She was a transgender and it was my first time interacting with, you know, the opposite sex to like the same thing that I liked or whatever, you know.
Like I said, God rest her soul. She's not here anymore, but she used to go through like
Like emotions like going up and down and shit like that or whatever
I more so thought she was bipolar, but I really didn't understand because like I said, that was my first time having a you know
So like somebody
When you shoot up estrogen once a week, especially a high dose of estrogen once a week, you get the full range of emotions.
Yeah, I really didn't know that. I thought she was bipolar because like to be honest, like to be 100% honest, I was diagnosed with bipolar and manic bipolar and manic ADHD when I was 12.
Her real name is Steve, but we called her Shug.
You know, that was like her nickname or whatever.
So when I met Shug, I was about like,
it was like a little after I lost my son so I was just now turning 19 so like I said as a present
moment I'll be I'll be 31 this year guys will say the same so you know I've known her for a while
but it was more so I've known her coming up into my adult years or whatever you know so of course
I knew you know trans existed and everything like that but you know the full you know the full
You don't just run into trans people on the daily, I mean, I guess that's something that
you can be good without knowing.
That was my first time, you know, like, it's not that I'm against it or anything like that.
Yeah.
I'm all for it, you know, love is love, you know, what makes you happy is what makes you
happy.
I'm, you know, I'm not.
homophobic whatsoever. So it's not that I was ever against it whatsoever. But, you know, like I
said, coming up into my adult years to where, you know, I was able to, you know, have cognitive
thoughts and understand, you know, I always knew that, you know, the same sex to like the same sex,
but being up close and personal and, you know, not trying to get to know the person, but,
you know, naturally getting to know a person because, you know, you guys, you know, that was my best friend,
So like I thought she was fucking bipolar or schizophrenic or something you know because we went out of town one time and
You know, I was driving and stuff like that and I would cut on like a song like you know
Like a little slow slow song or some shit like that or whatever
And she just got to crying out of nowhere like it was just like a
Flip like a switch or something like that like white and black
to ask her, I said, are you bipolar or something like that?
But I only asked her because I was speaking from experience
because I'm standing bipolar, you know?
So I'm like, I'm thinking to myself.
It's kind of confusing because my estrogen level is at 410.
And that's equivalent to someone that's
under second trimester.
So it's kind of hard.
So she had a huge feeling to me and everything like that.
It was just, you know.
I was you know just more so like like I said like getting up in person or whatever not
To know about it, but just naturally learning about it because that was
Close to
It's kind of hard to indem-
Because of the estrogen. I mean estrogen makes like women very emotional and like when you have a high amount of estrogen in you
I know they can cause the symptoms like that's why I'm saying like my estrogen level. It's very high
And I find my emotions still very crazy, you know, like, I mean, like, I was kind of one second, guys, I'm trying to charge it, but it's kind of hard for me to really comment on it because, like, as a kid, I've always had, like, mixed emotions, up and down type of thing.
And then when I got on estrogen, I mean, it just kind of made it a little bit worse, I guess.
So, did you have to get on any other medication to like, um, so with your like, for myself,
I don't, I don't like psychiatric medication for myself because I was on it as a kid and
it like made me gain weight.
I used to be on Seroquel and, um, that was the biggest weight gainer because I was on
it not as a PRN, which is supposed to be, but I was on it like as a daily of being like
It made me gain weight and I lost weight.
That was when you were a adolescent and you were a kid?
Yeah, this was when I was a kid.
And I haven't been on psych meds since I was a kid.
And then on any medications I'm on,
it's just my HRT regimen.
And I'm about to switch my regimen
because part of it I was put on depot provera.
And that shit makes you blow up.
the doctor from experience like I said guys will say the same I'll be 31
obviously you know I'm not old but I came a long way in a sense of you know the
car the hand that I was dealt you know
I don't think I know everything and I don't want to know everything because I feel like knowing just too much of anything
It's not good for anybody. Like what's the limit, you know
But I'm still a person that's willing to learn and not only am I willing to learn, you know
I don't want to just learn and not be able to you know, pass it on to the
I mean personally, I don't do the trans topics on my own channel because I'm just
I'm just a sex worker and I don't really want to have,
I don't want the risk of like,
you know, people not of age going,
coming across my platform,
because I'm talking about estrogen and shit.
It's gonna happen regardless.
Oh yeah, I mean, I do set my platform now for kids.
I do click on that, you know.
When I first got a hold to the streets and everything like that, I was 13 and what I mean by that is what I'm to put it in layman form.
What I mean by that is when I first jumped off the porch, as far as me, you know, I'm saying like having cognitive and understanding that the way that I was raised within my household is different on the outside.
And I was I was putting it as far as being like a quote-unquote sex worker
You are more than that. You know, that's just something. Oh, yeah
And just because you're going through whatever you want through we don't matter if you sell an orange is about a freeway
You know you talking to somebody. I don't sell pussy like bitch yourself girls got cookies. I'm just being 100%
You know I'm saying and um
I'm just being frank. I'm just keeping it 100, you know?
So like I said, I don't see some shit, but one thing about it, you said that, you know, you don't want to, you don't want to put front the things that you're going through and stuff like that because children, adolescents and stuff like that might be listening.
The thing about it is those are things that we cannot stop, but we can.
I, you know what I'm saying? In my eyes, I will see it as being detrimental because the things that I've learned when I was younger, you know what I'm saying?
I wish I had somebody to, you know, to show me and things like that.
And like I said, like, thank God, you know what I'm saying? Like God has been with me 100%, you know what I'm saying?
Like, without a doubt, you know, I've run into some scary things to where
The word is not even scary, you know, it's it's a word that's not even fucking made up in a dictionary yet
It's it's all right. I mean, I feel I feel safer in the hood than feeling then in the rich area
Because of how I grew up. I feel more safer in the ghetto than somewhere that's rich
So you're 23, right? Yes, but I mean
I don't mean I don't know more than any anybody whatsoever I'm learning things from you as well
I'm learning things from whoever's on this panel. You know what I'm saying? We all have that's the
thing like within our brains and stuff like that you know it's not for us to think about
gaining knowledge we naturally pick up on things you know you know saying things that we may need
in the future and the best thing that life has to offer for us is the things that we cannot pay for
You know I'm saying so therefore like I said, I'm learning from you and I'm not trying to you know
I'm saying like spill anything into your head for you to learn from me
Whatsoever, you know, it's just each one to each one pick it up as you go or whatever
And I'm not trying to make anybody out to be a believer, but please just know that
You know I'm saying you have a long way to go and don't define yourself as a sex worker or anything
That's just your that's just your testimony. That's it. It's just your testimony. I mean, yeah, I mean God
You know, it's your test, right? What's that's it, you know
Awesome do it and don't give up. Okay. I've come a long way in my life
I have been on my own since I was 16 years old and before that in and out of foster care and how to really like
difficult, crappy childhood.
And like now I'm a primary care provider
and I did all of that on my own.
Now I do have a lot of student loan debt,
but you can do anything you want to do.
And I would not consider myself incredibly intelligent either.
It just takes a lot of work.
And if you don't give up, you can,
like there's nothing in this world you can't have
if you wanted it up.
That's what I'm glad you said that, Sparky.
I'm so glad you spoke or whatever you're interjected. I thank you for that because
I'm struggling with survival's guilt right now. You know, um,
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, honey. I'm struggling with survival's guilt. And um,
you know, all I have is just me and my cat. Just me and my cat. I don't have any children.
You know, I don't want to have any children because of, you know, the way that I view things and because of my experience, I had a son, but my son passed away.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to shank you for every breath that you have and I know that survivor's guilt is the exact opposite feeling of that and
Just know you're you're wanted you're meant to be here. You're here and make something of it
You know take the shitty things that have happened to you and turn it into something good like
when when you really like get down to the the meat and potatoes of everything
that's happened to me I should be a complete bum asshole and I try so hard
to be nice to other people even when they're assholes because you never know
what somebody else is going through and you never know what somebody else is
having that like last moment
feeling in their life. And I don't think it's fun. I know
everybody likes to troll and it's cute. And I like to too. It's
fun. Don't get me wrong. But I think leading with kindness and
having these little moments where you meet somebody is having a
hard time online really make going online for me. And you know,
that's really lame for me to say, but no, no, no, no, no, no,
it's not lame whatsoever. That's what a lot of people lack in.
They lack in humanity. You know, they like freaking humanity.
Priceless thing you don't have to pay for that shit. You know I'm saying that's like you can give say like, okay
It's like you give somebody a hundred dollars, right?
and you give them a hundred dollars and the person that's accepting the that's receiving the hundred
dollars is oh thank you thank you god bless you god bless you you know and you know they mean it
from their heart but just as much as that hundred dollars mean to them the person that's given it
to them to the receiver you know they probably just doing it just because they got it but what I mean
is something that you can pick up and touch
Anything in this world that you can pick up and touch, it don't matter what it is, anything, whatsoever, your phone, your skin, your body, your eyes, your TV, anything that has a title and you can touch physically means nothing.
It means nothing, absolutely nada.
But the sense of humanity, having being able to have empathy and sympathy and, you know, fill those things and give it to somebody who needs it.
It's an incredible feeling.
So don't cut yourself.
Don't sell yourself short when you say it's lame and shit
like that.
That shit is not lame.
That shit is beautiful.
A lot of people don't have that shit.
And then when they fake it, like they do got it or whatever,
that shit come not even a dime a dozen, whatever.
Times that.
That shit doesn't mean anything.
People don't ever sell yourself short like that.
you know
Well, thank you. Nothing is lame about having humanity. That's a beautiful thing
And I'm sorry for what's happened. Just
There's no reason to be sorry the thing about it is
You know
My mom always tell me
Don't worry about the things that I can't change worry about the things that I can't change and
Um, I have like a spirit to wear. You know, I worry myself a lot
You know, I I literally just got out the hospital. It's my from like I said, God's will say the same
I'll be 31 August 3rd. You know, I'm freaking healthy from top to the bottom
You know, like I've never thought in my life that I would have to have you know a
surgery or be rushed to the hospital off of something that
you know I had no control over you know something that's natural that goes on within your body and
stuff like that your organs in shape you know and um it was like a freaking eye opener to me you
know my bad I had to do something real quick someone rang the door no worries babe oh my god
I wish I need I need some I just ran out like I thought okay I thought it was cute
I found some old pants I had like it didn't have like half a gram but it had
like a little bit in it I thought I thought I was gonna be cute and be able
to smoke it and have it for the rest of the day till tomorrow
No, I'm not a Debbie Downer, you know, I came I've been coming into
Sikes like live probably for about almost a couple months now, but this is my first time joining
You know, like honestly probably about three months now
I've been coming on enough to his live or whatever and not really speaking
I'm not the Debbie Downer and I hate to feel like that or whatever, but I'm just more so
I'm human
Yeah, it's not you guys. It's not you ladies. I'm talking about I'm reading a comment
He said something about a Debbie downer and I'm not explaining myself. I'm just you know
Passing on information, but yeah
I'm not trying to be a Debbie downer or anything. I hate that you look at it that way. I'm just I'm just human
You know
I'm just I'm here
Sorry, I'm looking down at the chat on my phone. And God, what the hell are you talking about?
I can't see really, so let me see.
You said Smunky's a Freak League, and I want to know what I did.
Who? My voice, Katrina? Thank you if you're talking about my voice.
I didn't say that, I just asked what made you say that.
With my teeth, Eldie.
Thank you, Sassy Scarlet. I appreciate it.
Oh, thank you, Katrina. Yeah, I get that a lot, and not like in bright
monitor or anything like that.
Guys, I do have a picture of 30 diamonds. You're gonna see 30 diamonds, and you're gonna be
seeing.
Oh, my God. It better not be better than my picture. Hey, we look alike.
What the fuck psyche?
Somebody had mentioned in the comments they said they like my
my heading my title my name the copacetic and
That's more or so. Just what life has taught me to be you know, just chill
You know, just chill and let shit play out.
That don't mean don't take evasive action
and, you know, get your life straight
when shit needs to, you know, be on time
and shit crunch time.
But just more so me being copacetic
has taught me just how to keep things at ease
and let things play out.
Which usually-
We do it side by side on my face.
Some other questions.
I would just hand them and let things, you know,
just happen the way they happen,
just based off my feelings and stuff like that.
when you sit sit back and let things play out, you know, it more than likely it works in your
favor. It works in my favor a lot. You know, um, far as me being out in the streets and having
to maneuver and deal with, you know, other human beings and, you know, things of that nature,
which is natural. But, you know, sometimes we live in this world and we just, we just all about self.
and that's more so understood because being all about self is more so about the hand that you're
dealt or maybe just the person that you naturally are. I've learned how to be more about self but
also be aware of other people and the people that I'm around or that I have to be around just
You know, so it's just more so just watching how you step and you know, recognizing when you done wrong and being able to, you know, understand that you're at fault and also till the opposite party that you're at fault and the reason why and so on and so forth.
You know,
They asked for your 5 o'clock shadow ways and they said it looked like I borrowed it.
Damn this shit.
Yeah I mean people say I have a whole beard and everything and I don't.
I'm going to show my ass hair if they want to see a 5 o'clock shadow.
Oh my god.
People in the comment sections are just really wild sometimes.
It goes from a little light light shit to crazier shit to like, which is really stupid how people are
I don't give a shit about what this is. Yeah, she doesn't bother me whatsoever
Like if I had my eyebrows micro micro bladed, I would totally go on camera right now, but I I don't
Yeah
I took my shower, laid down, studied a little bit, said my prayers, and ate the rest of
my Indian food.
Oh shit, nice.
I'm chilling, you know?
Going to bed?
You know what I'm saying?
I'm not by myself because of course, you know, I'm beautiful.
I have friends and stuff like that or whatever, but just me being solitude has kept me safe.
Has kept me safe not just physically, but just mentally as well like my emotions
I've done some shit that you know not purposely but just my brain the way my brain used to
You know process thought I never really used to process thought I just used to react and then
You know deal with the consequences later, but you know, thank God
you know, that, you know, I've, like I said, I've been around a block and back a few times,
you know what I'm saying? I've never been, you know, incarcerated. I don't have no tickets,
no, no anything, you know, um, you know, what's beautiful about going through all that bullshit?
The fucked up sense of humor you're going to have when you're older.
You're a perfect man.
You're gonna be so jaded and so fucking funny. It's gonna be great like net right now. You're in it and you're you're not
You know, oh, no, I don't know about it is even though
I totally you what you're saying a lot of things that I used to go through like when I was younger as far as like me
Like, you know, I used to fight a lot of shit when I was younger or whatever
You know, I was my aunt used to call me BA and
That was a nickname for me that she's that her heard herself. She's the freaking call me and shit
And I thought it was just my my first uh initial in my middle initial
So as I got older she said ba
PA you ain't made a glass, you know
It's just stand in front of TV and just sit there and just be zoned out watching TV while they you know
I'm saying why they trying to watch TV and shit
So one day I caught on to it and I turned around and they like oh shit
She know what that means, you know, because all that time I thought it was like her just calling my initials
But when she was saying calling me was badass badass, you know, I used to do a lot of a lot of shit that was um
I was caught I was a lot rough, you know more rough than the average girl and shit like that
Like I never played Barbie dolls. I used to like
Pick fights and shit like that or whatever one time I got my ass beat. I got my ass fucked up
Like I was known as like the little tough ass and shit.
So one day my cousin, we were walking and shit like that.
My cousin and her older friends or whatever,
they're like, oh, I can't stand her.
I'm like, who y'all talking about?
Who y'all talking about?
She's like, her right there.
Brienne, you can beat her ass.
Whoop her ass, Brienne, whoop her ass.
Man, that was the first time I really picked the fight,
but that was more so me having to understand
that I can't whoop everybody ass.
Cause I used to whoop ass when I was younger.
But the girl was like a year younger than me.
years old she was like probably nine or some shit so she was a little bigger than
you shit like that or whatever because she's like play sports and shit but I
was like a little friend a little girl and shit man that girl kicked my
she did the washing machine you know like the bitch did the washing machine
only oh my god like her fucking arms
Like, fuck you, don't fuck with me.
I haven't seen you since you showed everyone your fucking ass hair
on my fucking panel, you nasty.
Oh, she's rude.
I've never shown anybody that.
Dude, you fucking moved everyone on my panel.
You took a shit on my panel.
I just, you fucking spread your fucking ass hair,
you nasty shit fuck.
Yes, you did.
Then you fucking fell asleep on my fucking backstage.
You fell asleep.
Like you literally fucking went on my fucking panel took a fat shit
Everybody saw and heard you and then fucking you showed your nasty booty hair. Like what the fuck nope
Yeah, I haven't been on a panel with you since then
There's no rapping your savage if that's true. It was good. Yeah, I'm so cool
I mean, look, you drink a lot of vodka.
I showed myself taking a shit on stream.
That's awesome.
So the fucking comment tag is high signal 66.
I don't mean to interrupt you, people on here,
my fellow friends on here.
But to the people in the comments that's talking shit,
and it's only one particular person, really, or maybe two.
I really don't fucking know.
I just want to address this.
Shut the fuck up, OK?
Just shut the fuck or getting here and talk some shit
And then we'll see who's the bigger person on screen. I'm 411, but I'll make your ass feel small
Fuck you guys not not you people on here, but I'm talking about them
Fucking me can poop
Legs fall asleep. I'm gonna go get back in the bed, but anyhow
Anyway, so I just got my charger. So yeah, you did say you literally fucking took a shit on my panel and
It was gross
No light shit on you took a shit on your panel
You're you did see
That's not true. We're they were drinking that day. Yeah, as I am usually
Finish almost a full bottle of vodka that day
Yeah
Maybe I took a shit in the bathroom
This came and he paid me $300 to shit in his mouth and shit
That's actually how I met Boston
No, I don't believe that you guys you guys say that and that's not true
Nobody nobody nobody doesn't I think it's it on the one before people do that but not you guys
Let me tell you this signal. Let me tell you this. That's cap fucking Lutley
I know I know that there's people that like that, but I'm just saying not like not y'all
Y'all not getting paid for that. That's cap right now
Oh
When I speak of these things, I'm not speaking of them to glorify him
I'm speaking of them to it's the actual truth
It's not me just glorifying and put it on the pedal stool because I don't want anything anybody to go through with the fuck
I've been through
Seriously, and it's good as it sounds, you know shitting in somebody mouth for about 400 doesn't sound good
I mean, does that sound good to you?
As good as it sounds does that sound good to y'all I'll take a shit in your mouth
Somebody's mouth for about 500 bucks signal. I'm sure you fucking would
I'm saying I understand the mom. I understand the money
Reason, but I'm like you wanting to do that is crazy
It sounds like she does I'm joking
That's kind of me
Shits on the panel for free. No, that's
Yeah, yeah, okay. Thank you. Thank you flurry. Thank you
Thank you for rectifying that
This sounds like a point of pride for you, which is fine, which is fine
You so cute it looks like a carpet I know this is Miley
She is a pain in the ass, but I love her
No, I need to find this. I need to see if I believe
Disgusting it is absolutely see see like I said, you know what?
Got a fucking testimony. I don't have fucking chapters
I have volumes and the people that's listening whoever wants to listen or whatever like that
I'm not trying to make anybody to be a fucking believer you can believe whatever the fuck you want to believe you have that fucking right
Whether we're in a leisure of the free, you know, you have that right
Respectively are you are you African African-American person or
No, I'm I'm no I consider black. Absolutely. I'm considered black, but I'm I'm mixed
But I don't tell people like oh, I'm mixed, but I'm black. So, okay. Okay. Okay. I just
Haitian
In my Haitian
No, I'm human
Yeah, those are two different things
No, it's not you're you're not you're not from Haiti or just actually no way. No, yeah, I didn't mean it like that
I didn't mean it like that. I didn't mean it like that, but yeah, what's your what's your ethnicity?
Psyche the question that you are looking for is what is your ethnicity?
I'm not. I'm not. I'm not I'm
I'm not. I'm not. I'm not. I'm
Pick up on that. Yeah. What does he say? Yeah. Yeah. Sorry. Let me put my
No
No, no, no, no, that was a joke. That was a joke
Somebody said that in chat
Somebody said that in chat. Yeah, it is a joke. Yeah
Nobody said nobody said that that this is a white Tony panel
No, it's not like
I mean either way it's it's not it's not it's not this is not this is a diverse place for all people
It's a gay guy here
There's a gay guy here. You think you know everybody's allowed
There's a gay guy there's a transgender man here like everybody's allowed here
There's a black woman here, everybody's allowed here.
A white guy is a transgender, a transsexual.
I don't approve of racism, but I think racist jokes are funny.
Everybody's like, oh here we go, what is this?
She's gonna show the clip or I'm taking a shit.
Oh no, oh no.
Let's see it, let's see it.
Oh no, what is he doing?
wait no full screener let's see the clip it does not exist there is no clip
there's no clip of me ever taking a crazy that has never happened dude play
Are you atheists?
What?
No.
We're all different beliefs.
I'm a Catholic myself.
No.
We're all different beliefs.
We are all different races as well.
I don't care about race.
I don't see race.
Of course.
I don't see any...
i don't see any people that feel the human nature of being a being that god placed on his earth to
learn love and each one teach one and learn and love each other that's all i see but what he's
shown to me for no fucking reason i've been on this panel for more than fucking 30 minutes
and race has not even been a fucking topic until the the nobody it was it was just a it was just a
It's not it's not something that you need to take seriously
It's not it was a somebody made a joke it wasn't serious
We're not racist
That's not true
That never happened dude, are you crazy?
That was on my birthday
Hello
That has never happened
She's still going
Everyone let's say had a joker
Who is this lady with a dog? Is this your new? That's funky. It's funky. He's my friend
Is that who you got to replace me site? How dare you?
Yeah
She should she was she was much hotter
So you're gonna replace me with this. I'm gonna take a shot
Well, I don't replace it. We're gonna take a shot. Joker you left me. You left me Joker
Well, he left me you guys because he'll always love you more and you'll have a penis.
Say
Hey, mr. Beath, hey say
So, so hold on forty seven tell that the first tell that for you haven't held that
I'm sorry
Well, no Joker like subscribe to Florida diamonds only fans like what did you see on the only fans over?
What did you see the okay? So Florida diamond has the only fans and I know what she did
What she did was she poured milk all over herself and she said look I can produce milk
No, I didn't do that. I
Have the video on my Twitter. I have the actual video on my Twitter
And I mean if you want I can share the BW jacking off to me if you really want me to yeah sure
I
Off and squirt milk is like a superpower and I mean realistically. No because I
Because I remember how I said I have higher estrogen levels. Yeah, I can have breast milk because of having such a high estrogen level
And joke
No, the fuck is this
Sorry, so let's all let's all talk about something positive for a change
No, you can be negative
People psych
Negative, you know
Remember earlier when you were reading my you were reading my sign Leo August yeah
Yeah, I was gonna do whatever because I was just getting getting in the house and shit like that
I had the shower and eat and you know sand chill or whatever, but I was gonna ask you
Are you like into numerology?
Yeah
Okay, so when you were reading it or whatever, some of those things resonated like, uh, in effort like seriously, um, just more so like, um, like the basis of it or whatever and like, not too much but just the basis of it like, in a sense of quote unquote, I like danger in a sense, it's not more so me like liking danger and, you know, say have a knowledge to like, okay,
Just more so, you know, between a rock and hard place, you know,
faced with things that I know that I could have control before I got to that point.
So I was going to ask you, would you mind, I'm going to send you a link to,
I don't know if I could send, let me see, how can I, I could put it in the comments, right?
You get in the back chat you put in the back chat for sure. I can see the back shot. It is private chat in the backstage
You'll see
Yeah
Yeah, I'm sorry. It's me. It says it says back. There's private chat in the backstage. Well, what is it?
What is that picture?
Well, who is that one? What's going on here?
What Joker
Joker he cheated on you
Joker I thought we were together
You're what were you doing back there with three diamonds?
I recognize your belly. I recognize that belly
It's a fingerprint I recognize it
She's on me. I
Was trying to show off my god-given gifts
My god
What god gave me a wiener. What do you want me to do with it?
If people are paying that father's you then
Conditional love for even 40 diamonds I said 40 diamonds you need to upgrades
I don't understand it. She got really mad at me and she's like fuck you. No, I didn't you're the one that got excited over my content
What is that?
What's poking out of the front of the
I see her in the panel earlier, I think or whatever
Yes, of course go on just click on the link on the pin
You have it. Do you have you have more explicit ones? You can send me. I haven't dropped this video before
No
Okay
Joker Joker Joker whenever I go backstage you just you just leave immediately
I never shared it can't say I shared it because I never have
You did poor mom's like yeah, actually we saw the whole dancing that one time
Yeah, I'm gonna square this out. Well, no Joe. I didn't try to poor mommy. He just showed me his pubic hair one day
I was dancing. It was not for mom. Yeah. No, you whipped it out
No, I did I was dancing. You literally whipped it out for psyche
I was dancing
You whipped it. You whipped it out.
Yeah, so my first lesson speaking Spanish is
How do you okay, so you know in this world you go you can go a lot further when you know two languages, right? Yeah
Yeah, so
My my grandmother is um she's full of Puerto Rican but my grandfather is um he's um he's black
right so therefore like I said when you guys ask me what am I I don't like to say I'm mixed
even though I am but I I'm more so black that's what I am you know just I'm not racist or anything
by the way I'm sure you know that I don't think the guys on this panel is racist at all but yeah
I don't know a lot of Spanish to speak or whatever, but I know how to, if I was ever trapped on an island where people only spoke Spanish and I spoke English.
I know enough by being around my
my mom's side, my grandmother's side,
just to be able to turn around and maneuver in a sense.
I can survive, but I can speak Spanish,
but I can more so understand Spanish.
I probably don't even know how to read it in a sense,
but when my grandmother speaks,
I know how to understand it fluently
as if I know how to speak those words back to her,
but I don't know how to speak some of those words to her.
So I understand it more than I can speak it, right?
So,
I say, my abuelas, Morena y Boricua.
So then-
My grandmother's something.
My grandmother is black and Puerto Rican, right?
Okay, yeah.
So therefore, like I said,
like I only have a small percentage of that in me
or whatever you can tell by looking at me by my hair
and stuff like that in my skin, but whatever.
So,
How you say, um, I know how to speak a little bit of Spanish, so...
I know a little bit of Spanish.
My name is Jacobo, and I like to laugh.
I only know how to say I shit in your mother's cunt.
Oh my god.
I don't know how to say it in Spanish.
I'm listening. I'm listening. I know how to say uh
I want to say that word. I don't want to say that word. I do. I do. I do. I have a feeling I need to pull a card for a
card for um respectfully. I have a who do deck. I don't know if you respect or
But it is like a
European you know what I'm listening I'm intrigued those cards on other people as well
So I'm intrigued go ahead. I'll chime in after you're done. Okay. Okay
I'll just pull up a card because they have a lot of information in them
So just like thinking this card is like a big message for you. Okay, so this card for you. Okay. All right, cool. Okay
So you got this car. It says the mother of knives. I'll show you the whole school mother of knives
So this is the queen of swords. So there's a mother of knives
She's wearing it, you know, kind of a
Interesting uniform right there reading a book mother of knives queen of swords
Okay, and so mother of knives is usually queen of swords the queen of swords is someone that's you know been able to cut off a lot of
You know she's sometimes been through a divorce or a breakup, but just or just a cup to that of her life
It says her plant is the room it says the mother of knives is depicted here as a member of the two prestigious secret societies
The Grand United Order of the Odd Fellows and the Order of the Eastern Star in addition to the church mutual aid
Secret societies and fraternal and floral organizations were the backbone of black American communities
between the 18th and 20th centuries
Unlike women of other races, black women were welcome to participate and were respected as
powerful leaders and influencers of many of these organizations. Here, the mother of knives is a
powerful bibliomancer who uses the Bible as a guide, and it says the mother of knives is the
archetype of the warrior queen. On the positive side, she's perceptive, analytical, forthright,
Resilient highly intelligent deep and sets clear boundaries on the negative side. She's a perfectionist cold-hearted
aggressive and bitchy
Okay, and so that may
So that's a message for you
I don't know that if you represent that that queen of stores or is telling you to get more of the energy or the good qualities of it
See for the good qualities bad qualities or the negative qualities, you know, they're more they're more positive
But you know, you do have a lot of power as a queen of source energy being able to
No, cut people down with your words.
Yeah, they can be, they have its pros and cons,
but I see them as strengths.
They can have its pros and cons,
but just speaking from experience,
yeah, I definitely see those strengths.
I hear you though because I've been on the opposite side before I've been back and forth
There's it. So yeah, I definitely have for repositive for repositive quality
There's a shadow side to every positive quality because there's like give me there can be too much of the positive quality and
There and there there can be like, you know positive quality not they're not yep. It can be not
Yeah, not taken
Not a freaking series or whatever. Yep. Yeah
That was that was right on point
No, good
Joker do you want a card? Definitely
Joker no, you know Joker's good. Okay
Okay, did you get a who-do card today spunky or no? I think you gave me one earlier
Okay, well, we'll do it another time for a diamond. Do you want one more for a diamond a who-do card?
We can't we can't I like that dog's curly hair. Okay. Well, I guess diamond's away from her microphone
Guys if anybody wants to donate a membership I'll donate another one. I'll donate up to three more tonight
How do you have your cash up your bio or anything a cash up? Yeah by cash up
I could put a cash up in my in the banner on the screen, but and then if you'd like to
Yeah, but if anyone would like to
Donate some memberships I've had like that over 20 memberships past few days donated
You know, and I've been donating if I've been trying to donate as many as I can too
very appreciated
It just helps the show keep going and supports the show the show is gonna get a lot bigger
It's gonna be it's going places. I'm gonna I'm gonna help a lot of people too
With their shows, I'm gonna help people get started. I'm gonna help people to see that one. I think we can also see together
Jan's chicken army would like a card. Yeah, I got one from the villains deck for you Jan
They're just calling out to me this villains deck Jan chicken army gets this card. Okay, this
Okay, my dog likes your show
I don't know how to play the piano.
Why don't we all look everybody in the chat, look at Mr. Beast right here right now, look at me, look at me.
You see this ball right here? You see my background? I got a piano.
Anybody want to come over and play the piano?
Psyche?
Yeah, play the piano.
I don't know how to play the piano.
I know how to smoke weed though. So what do you guys think I should do with my hair? Should I shave it?
Sorry, go try to you. Yeah, I mean it looks a little bit fuzzy right now, but Jen that's it's a coin
Cut so I think you should cut it
That takes a coins jen it means it means like you know be generous and give you know
You know who to give to you and who needs are the most and you know just balance your generosity
But yeah, you're in a position to be generous and skip to the right people. Yeah, Joker your hair looks it looks like an afro
Right now, but how it wasn't so curly and wild
They're putting chemicals in the water
Pretty chemicals in the water. Well, that's nothing new
JT. Do you want to come up here Vicky Gulander Jan? Do you want to come up here?
We're hanging out
So you guys recently hear about this like I want to tell you this will be this crazy
So they did this thing at the ancient pyramids
right, they scanned it and they found out that there is
underneath the pyramids
It's giant pillars
They go all the way to the bike hundreds and what like two miles down
And then there's giant boxes underneath the billers and they're saying that's where the angels are very
Are you talking about like under the sphinxes paws because I've always heard about these the
These uh, what was does anyone know what they let's call but it's like right under the sphinx's paws
They're supposed to be the ancient records room and no
This is under the pyramids. They did under all three and under it needs all three of these giant pillars and going around the pillars
The staircases all the way down underneath the pyramids and it goes down like a mile
Well, cool, you know, I said, I don't know that be you know, there's the Egyptians don't really that anybody
They're poking around those pyramids these days, you know, it's like it's kind of like
They're kind of, they don't let anybody explore them anymore.
No one's let us spend the night in them
or go to the King's chamber anymore.
But yeah, they're interesting places.
Well, the reason why they don't want anyone to explore it
is because it's going to change the narrative
that the Egyptians built that.
That's what they think.
They think the Egyptians built it
and the Egyptians were this futuristic society.
When in reality, there was a futuristic society
that built it.
And then the Egyptian just built on top of it. You see what I'm saying? Yeah. Yeah
That's Joker who's talking guys, it's a Joker Joker. Why can't I see I can't see him
Hey, hey hands off bitch, that's my boyfriend
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I don't like that information. Hey Joker Joker Joker Joker Joker dance for a little bit dance for a little bit
Look he's on the screen
Yeah, oh guys here we go. Yeah, I like you should braid your hair
That's that's all I got. Okay. It's all you got right now. Thank you Joker. I like this
Here you can have you can have
Yoki machine can you hear the microphone? Is it echoing?
Like Mike check check
No numerology, yeah, well, do you know your life path number?
I'm gonna start rapping. I'm gonna start rapping. You're rapping? Okay. Yo, yo. You guys are karaoke. Okay, this is number seven. Seven are awfully deeply spiritual in many cultures placed in enormous amount of spiritual significance on the world.
You're number seven? Are you number seven or is that your life path or is that your like just the number day you're born? Yeah, my life path is number seven.
So it says sevens are awfully deep spiritual. I'm sorry
No, no go ahead. I want to hear what this is number seven guys if you know your life. Can you hear me still?
Sevens, can you hear me?
Good
You can hear me right? Yes. We hear you good
Sevens are often deeply spiritual and many cultures place an enormous amount of spiritual significance on the number seven.
They are gifted with a natural insight and a demeanor which places thought and strength of character before action and impulse.
Sevens are intelligent and capable of analyzing situations and problems at a deeper level than most others.
Sevens are well springs and a knowledge of information on a broad variety in subjects.
The internal students are always reading and learning and absorbing information from the
world around them.
Sevens tend to be awfully and deeply psychological about great and many things, although they
often do not realize how insightful they are.
Sevens are not usually egotistical and often underestimated upon the depths of their perception
Sevenths tend to be private people sharing information about themselves with
their family and closest friends. Private time isn't more important to them and
much of their time is spent thinking, reading, or learning in one way or
another. Sevenths tend to be very focused when they work demanding of a high
level of perfection for themselves and while
Some sevens go through social phases in their lives.
They usually return frequently to moments
of their pure stillnesses and solitude
because that is the truest of their nature.
See, remember I said something about like me being a solitude?
Like I love, I love solitary.
I love me being, you know, too much
because it keeps me, you know, safe in a sense of mentally,
physically, yeah, but my mental state, you know,
like with me being diagnosed with bipolar disorder,
when I was 12, you know, I don't take my medicine for it. I only take my ADHD medication or I take
my anxiety medication. I don't bipolar medication anymore, you know, but um, me being diagnosed,
you know, and, you know, not taking my medication or whatever and just, you know, finding ways to
for me to be able to maneuver so I won't need that medication, you know, um, like me being
You know, I've got some crazy things just based on you know me being hurt
You know like trying to like I tried to kill myself and shit like that or whatever because somebody hurt me so bad or whatever
You know like mentally, you know
Yeah, anyway
And uh, okay, thank you for sharing your stories to you. I want you to listen to
Last time it says the downside sevens can become so isolated it will touch with their friends and society
Sevens can also lack an ambition and energy to put their thoughts into motion
They master they are masters of theory and thought and ideas
But they may lack the spark to turn on ideas into the reality other sevens may become may become depressed
negative or often become too withdrawn. In relationships,
sevens are very devoted to the home but may become overwhelmed because they need space.
Sevens have great strength of character and will go to a distance for others they love.
But if sevens does not have time to think or reflect or spend time on their own,
he or she may become imbalanced, stressed, or agitated until time can be made for themselves.
True very good. Absolutely. Yeah, very true and guys
Look as you can look up your life path number by just adding up all the digits of your birthday
You know, if it's like they've been March 6 1966 you go 3 plus 6 plus 1 plus 9 plus 6 plus 6
It'll get down to like a couple numbers unless it's like 11 22 or 33. You just keep reducing it until
It gets a single digit. That's your life path number. And you can look that up and then there'll be a lot of interesting information because
Listen to him
Thoroughbred says
Thoroughbred?
Oh, yeah, so Psyche does not give one fuck what she's oh, hold on. I'm busy looking in Joker's eyes. Yeah, I am
I think he's calling you. That's a long way of saying that you're, uh, G-A-Double-Y.
Uh, P-P-What? Hold on. I'm gonna get my piece out of it. I'll be back.
What are you saying? I'm in what?
He said you're gay.
G-A-W-Y. Oh, it's okay. I'm in cold.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm back.
You came back right when I came back, girl. Oh, I will try to get a
juice. That's one of the juice with me. So,
Spunky, if you ever got the hookup, I would want to get you a
Why do you guys call him gay?
You're judging people based off what they love and, you know, they're like, they're just like, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not, that's not,
I'm not, and if I do read it wrong, I know you guys,
I know you ladies are homophobic or anything like that
or whatever, just based off me being on here with you guys
for almost an hour and talking and stuff.
I know that for a fact.
But when I read these comments on the right side
of the screen, I'm not reading the names.
I can't even, you know what I'm saying,
understand who is who or whatever like that.
I'm just reading the comments.
Yeah.
Hey guys, there's so many members they spunkies remember and can you guys stop talking about the ladies on here on the
Gay or trans these are human beings
She's a woman and that's a guy and he can like whatever he wants to like and flirty is a woman. I don't care
mean Joker he had a fun time with me so I just want them to address you guys as
you let you as what you are and you're a woman and that's what you are in he can
like in psyche can like whatever he wants to like so I want to now be
referred to as God and God he can no longer be God okay okay
Got it. That's fine. Okay. I mean
Why did Joker leave?
I have beef with Joker and I was gonna argue with him. Oh shit. You're gonna get a pizza in the oven or something
So why is this so true like this? Like
This is crazy. Well, there's no truth between Joker and I
Mind blowing. I offer some treasure videos to Kate
I'm kidding.
Daddy, what's my status?
This is not smart.
It will represent a long struggle in finding a harmony between the difference of forces and goals with them on life
The balance work versus play is others versus self in between all things in life and requires the flexibility which is yes
We are those when you are to the store and you leave us outside in your bike. Is it is it your phone or like an iPad?
Why are you leaving your phone you're fucking by?
I know.
No biggie.
Someone steals.
Someone's.
Who's burping?
Who's that?
What the fuck?
Sorry.
Yeah, who was that squeaky noise when you were at the store?
It was like.
It was my breaks.
Oh my gosh.
That is like the most like, what the fuck?
I was just burping.
What was that?
That was me.
Oh, that was you.
Oh my gosh.
Well, it's in a trap. It's botched in plans
My gosh, I'm kind of shocker it. I just can't believe
No, no, no, it's fine. It's fine. We're human
Yeah, oh, yeah
I'm letter rip
Yeah
Sike wasn't a thong show ring before
I want to, I want to send you something.
I want to send you a photo, right?
And if you can share this photo with the viewers,
I want you to do that as well.
So, um,
the photo of me and my Speedos.
I can send you a selfie.
That's what I have as my guest, thank you.
Oh my God.
Can you tell me how to see you?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, I can I can say, hey, hey, um, so did I mean I can be so did I mean can be you can be share all of a sudden
They say I love one
Before we know our money is all been spent
Oh, no
Summer I deleted your name. I said I untagged you. I untagged you. I never said the leader the videos
I just untagged you
I said that earlier
You got me baby. I got you babe. It was a joke. I got you babe a fucking joke. I got you babe
No, not you I'm talking about fucking botched implants. He doesn't want to take a joke. Who's his boss implants. We're talking
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Isn't it ridiculous? It's so ridiculous. So Chris. Yeah, Christine God you are come up. Who wants to come up?
I'm not seeing very many
You could speak come up. I'll argue with you
You got you got to come on go, you know the place. I want to be I want to I want to be Tupac. Okay, there's you fuck
Okay
Me against the world
We're gonna do
Let's welcome summer to the show
Yeah, you
Shut the fuck up. Fuck what you talking about bitch? You don't know what the fuck's going on
I don't want to be in the bullshit. I told you that
So I go back and play the video man
I'm still in the-
Did someone give a fuck what you're talking about respectfully?
Suck a dick!
I don't want to get in the bullseye!
She's gonna get to pay for the play of music!
Who's playing music?
Respectfully dumb cut!
I don't want to play music, it doesn't fucking matter, she can't play some instrumental music, like that's not how they say it, they strike 10 for us and she's instrumental far.
Thank you, are you okay?
You don't want no music.
Are you okay?
I don't know, what's going on JJ?
What's going on? Are you okay? You look great.
Just come back on nothing on my platform. So therefore
Are you okay?
I know you ain't talkin'
I know you ain't talkin' with that flabby motherfuckin' ass
that flabby ass goddamn stomach you bad bitch
You have bad goals
Where? Where bitch?
Where?
It's like my dick
I'm twice your age and I still act before a woman
and look better than you
Shut the fuck up, ain't nobody talkin'
No, that would be diamond
That would be diamond
That would be dying with the dick.
It would be dying with the dick.
It's okay.
I know you ain't talking.
Hold on, wait. Let me get those.
Okay, I can look old.
But you know what? What I don't look like
is a fake fucking cut.
Okay, I'm not jealous of your...
Okay, okay.
Why don't you go sell some more guys this?
I don't see no...
You can never be jealous of me.
You're not a woman, bitch.
You don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be, you don't want to be
You're a man, you're doing it again.
It's an inverted penis, it's an inverted penis.
I'm literally gonna have a pussy this year.
No, it's an inverted penis.
Hey, we're texting.
Are you a people on the baton?
Hey, I don't bitch get a better mic.
How about that, you dumb bitch?
Fuck you.
It's not a pussy.
It's not a pussy, it's an inverted penis.
It doesn't care.
What the fuck are you?
Shut the fuck up, you stupid little fucking cunt.
Get a better mic, bitch.
I'm not a child. I'm 31. Are you okay? I'm okay. Okay. Are you okay? Yeah. Yeah, you just I've never seen you
I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I'm not echoing, I
I don't know. There's something in your eyes that looks different. I
Little bit
Hey guys, how are we doing guys? I know
Not a kid, I'll be 31 August 3rd, August 3rd, 1994.
I was born on a fuckin' Wednesday.
I'm fuckin' right here.
You do kinda sound like Jennifer Loewis
from the hood.
I want you to listen to this.
I'm actually fuckin' black.
And I'm-
What do you even fuck what you are?
Shut the fuck up, child.
You sound like a little fuckin' kid.
No one gets the fuck, bitch.
You think you're sticking to our blue bubble, bitch?
No blue bubble, we don't give a fuck.
Could you say I'm still Jenny from the block?
already diamond is an AI video with me in it and I will strike this page.
Whoa. Wow. You're right. I will. She made an AI video and she just played it.
What were you doing? On my show? On your show. Just now. Wow. You're going to strike a channel.
Wow. Yes, I will. Yes, I will. You're a fake out there. I don't care.